Faculty Women's Club. Minutes of general meetings. 1932-2000.
UCLA Library Special Collections
Faculty Women's Club. Minutes of general meetings.
1932-2000
University Archives Record Series 361
UCLA Library Special Collections
0.2 linear ft. (1 box)
Record Series 361 contains the minutes of general meetings held by UCLA's Faculty Women's Club. Files also include agendas from 1942-1943 and 1997-1998.
Faculty Women's Club.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Scope and Content
Record Series 361 contains the minutes of general meetings held by UCLA's Faculty Women's Club. Files also include agendas from 1942-1943 and 1997-1998.
This is an active record series; additional University records are expected to be added.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 3466889
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1932-1933. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  General note
  Officer: Elizabeth Klingberg.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1933-1934. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Officer: Florence A. Wilson.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1934-1935. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Officer: Bertha Haines.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1935-1936. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Officer: Effie Shambaugh.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1936-1937. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Officers: Mary Upham/Sarah Adsatt.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1937-1938. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Officer: Maria Lopez de Lowther.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1938-1939. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Officer: Eleanor H. Johnson.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1939-1940. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Officer: Kate Gordon Moore.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1940-1941. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Officer: Maude R. Murdoch.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1941-1942. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Officer: Clara Humphreys.
- General meetings - agenda of meetings., 1942-1943. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Officer: Daphne H. Daus.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1942-1943. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1943-1944. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Officer: Margaret Carhart.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1944-1945. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Officers: Louise C. Anderson/Katherine McLaughlin.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1945-1946. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Officer: Bernice Hooper.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1946-1947. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Officer: Emma Skillman Stone.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1947-1948. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Officer: Hansena Frederickson.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1948-1949. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Officer: Alice Moreman.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1949-1950. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Officer: Gertrude D. Huberty.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1950-1951. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Officer: Dorothy Robbins.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1951-1952. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Officer: Archine Fetty.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1952-1953. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Officer: Hazel Hoel.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1953-1954. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Officer: Betty Staaks.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1954-1955. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Officer: Viola L. Warren.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1955-1956. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Officer: Evelyn Hodgson.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1956-1957. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  Officer: Joyce S. Nelson.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1957-1958. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Officer: Carmela Speroni.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1958-1959. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Officer: Ann Sumner.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1959-1960. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Officer: Lillian Asimow.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1960-1961. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  Officer: Brownie Pucket.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1961-1962. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  Officer: Grace Handy.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1962-1963. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  Officer: Helen B. Boelter.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1963-1964. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  Officer: Jeanne Durham.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1964-1965. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  Officer: Louise York.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1965-1966. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  Officer: Janice Hamilton.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1966-1967. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  Officer: Nancy Leondes.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1967-1968. (Box 1, Folder 37)
  Officer: Mary Erickson.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1968-1969. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  Officer: Pat Hardwick.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1969-1970. (Box 1, Folder 39)
  Officer: Barbara Comrey.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1970-1972. (Box 1, Folders 40-41)
  Officer: Sylvia Winstein.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1972-1973. (Box 1, Folder 42)
  Officer: Penny Hutchinson.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1973-1974. (Box 1, Folder 43)
  Officer: Joanne Knopoff.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1974-1975. (Box 1, Folder 44)
  Officer: Barbara La Force.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1975-1976. (Box 1, Folder 45)
  Officer: Audrey Marrocco.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1976-1977. (Box 1, Folder 46)
  Officer: Eva Orbach.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1977-1978. (Box 1, Folder 47)
  Officer: Bee Welmers.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1978-1979. (Box 1, Folder 48)
  Officer: Pat Nagy.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1979-1980. (Box 1, Folder 49)
  Officer: Sonny Harris.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1980-1981. (Box 1, Folder 50)
  Officer: Dianne Homsher.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1981-1982. (Box 1, Folder 51)
  Officer: Sandy Spolsky.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1982-1983. (Box 1, Folder 52)
  Officer: Jane Jones.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1984-1986. (Box 1, Folders 53-54)
  Officer: Helen Nefkens.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1987-1988. (Box 1, Folders 55)
  Officer: Jean Serafetinides.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1991-1992. (Box 1, Folders 56)
  Officer: Elizabeth Cecchetti.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1993-1994. (Box 1, Folders 57)
  Officer: Ann Sprowls.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1994-1995. (Box 1, Folders 58)
  Officer: Diana Hawthorne.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1995-1996. (Box 1, Folders 59)
  Officer: Marinette Kubeck.
- General meetings - agenda of meetings., 1997-1998. (Box 1, Folders 60)
  Officer: Felicite Halma.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1997-1998. (Box 1, Folders 61)
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1998-1999. (Box 1, Folders 62)
  Officer: Sari Halasz.
- General meetings - minutes of meetings., 1999-2000. (Box 1, Folders 63)
  Officer: Margaret Churchill.